<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Device Control</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p>StellarProtect/StellarProtect (Legacy Mode) agent supports one-time USB access
                permission on site; while StellarOne console offers permanent USB access permission
                via remote configuration. For the local agent, when USB device control has been
                enabled, every time users plug in USB devices, the agent will prompt a message for
                users to confirm if the USB device access is allowed. On top of that, StellarOne
                users with administrator or operator role can add trusted USB devices into the
                    <uicontrol>Device Control</uicontrol> list, allowing the specified devices to
                access directly without further check, thus facilitating the trusted USB access for
                good.</p>
            <note id="note_ysz_m4d_jvb">
                <p>In addition to USB drives, StellarProtect (Legacy Mode) also supports blocking
                    CD/DVD drives and floppy disks on managed endpoints. </p>
            </note>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>All</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/POLICY"/></cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_kqb_dvc_jvb">
                        <p><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/POLICY_NOTE"/></p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Make sure the <uicontrol>Device Control</uicontrol> toggle is switched
                    on.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click <uicontrol>Add</uicontrol>. The <wintitle>Add Trusted USB
                        Device</wintitle> window appears.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Specify at least one of the following information for the trusted USB
                    device.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul id="ul_n4r_sjn_n5b">
                        <li>
                            <p><uicontrol>Vendor ID</uicontrol></p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p><uicontrol>Product ID</uicontrol></p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p><uicontrol>Serial number</uicontrol></p>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click <uicontrol>OK</uicontrol> to complete the setting.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Check if the USB device is successfully added in the device control list.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>(Optional) To edit the USB device information, select the USB device and click
                    the edit icon under the <uicontrol>Actions</uicontrol> header. A pop-up window
                    appears. Edit the USB device information in the related text fields and then
                    click <uicontrol>OK</uicontrol>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>(Optional) To remove a USB device from trusted list, choose either way listed
                    below. </cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul id="ul_d4k_qkn_n5b">
                        <li>
                            <p>For removing mutiple USB devices at the same time, select the USB
                                devices and click the <uicontrol>Delete</uicontrol> button next to
                                the <uicontrol>+Add</uicontrol> button.</p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>For removing only one USB devices, click the edit icon under the
                                    <uicontrol>Actions</uicontrol> header.</p>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                    <p>A pop-up <uicontrol>Notification</uicontrol> window appears. Click
                            <uicontrol>Confirm</uicontrol> to delete the USB device(s).</p>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
