<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Configuring Scan Component for
        StellarOne</title>
    <taskbody>
        <steps id="steps_vyt_vgr_m5b">
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Administration</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>Downloads/Updates</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>StellarOne</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>To start the component update for StellarOne immediately, click the
                        <uicontrol>Update Now</uicontrol> button under <wintitle>Scan
                        Component</wintitle> section.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_qhm_r3r_m5b">
                        <p>
                            <ul id="ul_t4m_fjr_m5b">
                                <li>
                                    <p>By clicking the <uicontrol>Update Now</uicontrol>, StellarOne
                                        will download and update the latest components. All of the
                                        pattern and engine versions available are listed under the
                                            <uicontrol>Update Now</uicontrol> button.</p>
                                </li>
                                <li>Users can refer to the <uicontrol>Last Updated:</uicontrol> next
                                    to the <uicontrol>Update Now</uicontrol> button for the last
                                    time the scan component was updated.</li>
                            </ul>
                        </p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>To schedule for the component update, toggle on the <uicontrol>Schedule
                        Update</uicontrol> under the <wintitle>Scan Component Update
                        Schedule</wintitle>.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul id="ul_mhm_gnr_m5b">
                        <li>
                            <p>Click the radio buttons under <uicontrol>Frequency</uicontrol> to set
                                the frequency by <uicontrol>Daily</uicontrol>,
                                    <uicontrol>Weekly</uicontrol>, or
                                    <uicontrol>Monthly</uicontrol>.<note id="note_nkj_h4r_m5b"
                                    type="important">
                                    <p>Since not every month has the date 29th, 30th, or 31st, e.g.,
                                        Feburary only has 28 days (29 days on a leap year), it is
                                        recommended to select <uicontrol>The last day of the
                                            month</uicontrol> for monthly update frequency. This
                                        helps prevent the system from bypassing the update in the
                                        month that does not have certain dates.</p>
                                </note></p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>Click the <uicontrol>Start Time</uicontrol> to determine when to
                                start the scheduled scan component update.</p>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>To specify the download source for StellarOne regarding different network
                    configurations, select one of the radio buttons under <uicontrol>Scan Component
                        Update Source (StellarOne)</uicontrol> .</cmd>
                <choices id="choices_dmz_jbh_3vb">
                    <choice>
                        <p>If the StellarOne server can connect to the ActiveUpdate server, select
                            the <uicontrol>ActiveUpdate server</uicontrol>, the component update
                            will be downloaded directly from the ActiveUpdate server.</p>
                    </choice>
                    <choice>
                        <p>If the StellarOne server can not connect to the ActiveUpdate server or if
                            users host an update server in an internal network,  select
                                <uicontrol>Other update source</uicontrol> and specify the URL
                            address in the text field.</p>
                    </choice>
                </choices>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>To specify the download source for agents regarding different network
                    configurations or agent types, select one of the radio buttons under
                        <uicontrol>Scan Component Update Source (Agents)</uicontrol>.</cmd>
                <choices id="choices_x13_d2h_3vb">
                    <choice>If the agents can connect to StellarOne server, select <uicontrol>Update
                            from StellarOne</uicontrol> to download the component update source
                        directly from the StellarOne server.</choice>
                    <choice>
                        <p>If the agents can not connect to StellarOne server or if they are
                            standalone agents, select <uicontrol>Other update source</uicontrol> and
                            specify the URL address in the text field.</p>
                    </choice>
                </choices>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
