<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Notification and SMTP Settings</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p>The settings allow users to receive notifications of warning or outbreak events by
                emails.</p>
        </context>
        <steps id="steps_pt3_g3m_m5b">
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Administration</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>SMTP Settings</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade> for specifying the SMTP server setting required for notification
                    sending.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Specify the <uicontrol>Server address</uicontrol>, <uicontrol>Port</uicontrol>,
                    and <uicontrol>Sender</uicontrol>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>(Optional) If the SMTP server requires authentication, click the checkbox next
                    to <uicontrol>SMTP server requires authentication</uicontrol>. Specify the
                        <uicontrol>User name</uicontrol> and <uicontrol>Password</uicontrol> as the
                    SMTP server authentication credential.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the <uicontrol>Send Test Email</uicontrol> button to send a test email
                    from StellarOne (This step is essential for Step 12).</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol> to complete the SMTP setting.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Administration</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>Notification</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade> for notification criteria and email setting.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Under the <uicontrol>Warning Level Agent Events</uicontrol>, click the
                        <uicontrol>Send warning level agent events</uicontrol> toggle to enable
                    it.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_ywl_nd4_m5b">
                        <p>When the switch under <uicontrol>Warning Level Agent Events</uicontrol>
                            is enabled, StellarOne console will send a notification to your email
                            when an incident that triggers a “<b>Warning</b>” happens.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Under the <uicontrol>Outbreak</uicontrol>, click the <uicontrol>Send outbreak
                        notifications</uicontrol> toggle to enable it.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_pc3_xd4_m5b">
                        <p>When the switch under <uicontrol>Outbreak</uicontrol> is enabled,
                            StellarOne console will send a notification to your email when more than
                            a specified number of open warning messages have appeared in a specified
                            time period.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Define an outbreak by the number of detections and the detection period.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ul id="ul_sg1_q24_m5b">
                        <li>
                            <p>Specify the number of occurrences of an event in the field of
                                    <uicontrol>Number of warnings in a time period</uicontrol> (1-
                                20000).</p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>Specify the time frame during which the event has occurred in the
                                field of <uicontrol>The time period of those warnings</uicontrol> (1
                                - 60 minutes).</p>
                        </li>
                    </ul>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Under <uicontrol>Email Notifications</uicontrol>, specify the email address for
                    receiving the notifications in the <uicontrol>Send to</uicontrol> field.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click <uicontrol>Save</uicontrol> to complete the setting.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to the specified email box to check if you receive the test email sent from
                    StellarOne (refer to Step 4).</cmd>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
