<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">OT Application Safeguard</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p><uicontrol>OT Application Safeguard</uicontrol> is an industrial-based change control
                protection. This feature ensures the StellarProtect-recognized OT applications to be
                updated without being blocked or restricted. In addition, users can enable OT
                application protection to secure recognized OT application executable binary
                    files.<note id="note_ynd_s5b_s5b">
                    <p>Upon launch, StellarProtect will auto-detect currently-installed OT
                        applications and put them under protection. The recognized OT applications
                        will be shown on the <uicontrol>General Info</uicontrol> tab page.</p>
                </note></p>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol> tab in the top navigation bar of the
                    StellarOne web console. </cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the <uicontrol>All </uicontrol>group on the <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol>
                    screen. The <wintitle>Agents</wintitle> screen displays a list of agents managed
                    by StellarOne.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Navigate to the target agent or agent group and click the Policy icon under the
                        <uicontrol>Actions</uicontrol> header.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>The <uicontrol>General Info</uicontrol> screen appears. Check the OT
                    Applications automatically recognized by the StellarProtect agent.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_nz2_5zm_n5b">
                        <p>Be sure to enable the <uicontrol>Maintenance Mode</uicontrol> before
                            installing new OT applications. After the installation process
                            completes, disable the <uicontrol>Maintenance Mode</uicontrol> and then
                            StellarProtect will auto re-scan the newly-added OT applications. Any
                            new applications found will be added into the OT Application Safeguard
                            list. Please refer to <xref
                                href="sPconfigureMaintenanceMode=20220802170455.xml"/> for how to
                            enable this function.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Users can also manually add the installation path for the application into the
                    Safeguard’s protection list.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol id="ol_mmj_t2n_n5b">
                        <li>
                            <p>Click the <uicontrol>Policy</uicontrol> tab and scroll down and find
                                the <uicontrol>OT Application Safeguard</uicontrol> at the left side
                                of the screen.</p>
                        </li>
                        <li>Make sure the <uicontrol>OT Application Safeguard</uicontrol> toggle is
                            switched on.</li>
                        <li>
                            <p>Click <uicontrol>File/Folder</uicontrol>, and then a pop-up window
                                appears.</p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>Click the <uicontrol>+Add</uicontrol> button, and then select
                                    <uicontrol>Folder</uicontrol> or <uicontrol>File</uicontrol> and
                                specify the folder or file path in the corresponding text
                                fields.</p>
                            <note id="note_m4g_zcn_n5b">
                                <p>By default StellarProtect will only protect the PE files
                                        (<filepath>.exe</filepath> and <filepath>.dll</filepath>)
                                    under the selected folder and its subfolder(s).</p>
                            </note>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>(Optional) If users want to protect all files inside the selected
                                folder, please uncheck the <uicontrol>Executable files
                                    only</uicontrol> radio button. </p>
                            <note id="note_zqf_qdn_n5b" type="tip">
                                <p>By unchecking the <uicontrol>Executable files only</uicontrol>
                                    option, users can prevent their own secret files,
                                    configurations, or other files under the selected folder from
                                    being modified.</p>
                            </note>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>Click <uicontrol>Add</uicontrol> to complete the setting.</p>
                        </li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Users can also add user-defined processes.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol id="ol_kmv_q2n_n5b">
                        <li>
                            <p>Go to <menucascade>
                                    <uicontrol>Policy</uicontrol>
                                    <uicontrol>OT Application Safeguard</uicontrol>
                                </menucascade>, and then click the <uicontrol>Authorized
                                    Processes</uicontrol> option.</p>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>A pop-up window appears. Click the <uicontrol>+Add</uicontrol>
                                button, and then specify the authorized processes in the
                                corresponding text fields.</p>
                            <note id="note_lqk_3fn_n5b" type="important">
                                <p>By adding the authorized process, users may set other
                                    applications to be trusted and change the protected
                                    files/folders previousely defined as well as the PE files for OT
                                    applications detected by agents. Please note if any malicious
                                    file has been set into the authorized process, StellarProtect
                                    cannot prevent this file from modifying the OT applications
                                    since it has been already excluded from the StellarProtect’s
                                    monitoring process. Make sure the user-defined authorized
                                    process is safe before adding it.</p>
                            </note>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            <p>Click <uicontrol>Add</uicontrol> to complete the setting.</p>
                        </li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
