<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Patch</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p>The <uicontrol>Patch</uicontrol> function allows the administrator to deploy a patch
                file upgrade on all agents under the same group policy. The patching process can be
                conducted remotely and automatically using policy synchronization. Only one patch
                file (Agent version) is allowed to be upgraded every time under each group
                policy.</p>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol> tab in the top navigation bar of the
                    StellarOne web console. The <wintitle>Agents</wintitle> screen displays a list
                    of agents managed by StellarOne. Navigate to the target agent or group and click
                    the corresponding <uicontrol>Policy Inheritance </uicontrol>link.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Scroll down and find the <uicontrol>Patch</uicontrol> at the bottom right
                    corner of the screen.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the checkbox next to the version of the patch file for deployment.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_wxd_rcv_z5b">
                        <p>Users can import new patches for the agent on the <xref
                                href="downloadUpdates=20220803181908.xml"/> page.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>The selected patch file will be deployed on the agents under the same group
                    policy.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_bch_yjk_n5b">
                        <p>Since StellarProtect is able to use global policies for all agents as
                            well as group policy for group-owned machines to conduct the patching
                            process on multiple devices, before you select agent version please note
                            the following: <ul id="ul_gtf_ckk_n5b">
                                <li>
                                    <p>Global policy is the default agent landing policy, so every
                                        agent will apply this policy first before moving to other
                                        groups. We suggest that the global policy should use lower
                                        agent version as its base policy.</p>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <p>If you don't want to set any agent version for patch
                                        deployment, please unclick all checkboxes next to the agent
                                        version patch files in the <uicontrol>Patch</uicontrol>
                                        section.</p>
                                </li>
                            </ul></p>
                    </note>
                </info>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_tt4_tkk_n5b" type="important">
                        <p>StellarProtect Agent 1.0 does not support remote patch because it does
                            not have any available remote patch files.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
