<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Patch</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p>The <uicontrol>Patch</uicontrol> function allows the administrator to deploy a patch
                file upgrade on all agents under the same group policy. The patching process can be
                conducted remotely and automatically using policy synchronization. Only one patch
                file (Agent version) is allowed to be upgraded every time under each group
                policy.</p>
            <note id="note_idg_lrv_pvb" type="important">
                <p>A patch is generally used to fix or enhance the current version. If you
                    accidentally patch an older version, the patch deployment should not work and
                    the agent status will keep un-synced with the StellarOne console. Meanwhile,
                    other policy settings can't be deployed, either. After 20 minutes the agents
                    will resynchronize with StellarOne; until then can the policy settings be
                    applied to the agent.</p>
            </note>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>All</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/POLICY"/></cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_kqb_dvc_jvb">
                        <p><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/POLICY_NOTE"/></p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Scroll down and find the <uicontrol>Patch</uicontrol> at the bottom right
                    corner of the screen.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the checkbox next to the version of the patch file for deployment.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_wxd_rcv_z5b">
                        <p>Users can import new patches for the agent on the <xref
                                href="downloadUpdates_agent_patch=20221028151831.xml"/> page.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>The selected patch file will be deployed on the agents under the same group
                    policy.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_bch_yjk_n5b">
                        <p>Since <ph conkeyref="PRODvars/PRODUCT_SP_ALTERNATIVE_NAME"
                                >OFFICIAL_PRODUCT_NAME</ph>/<ph
                                conkeyref="PRODvars/PRODUCT_SPLM_ALTERNATIVE_NAME"
                                >OFFICIAL_PRODUCT_NAME</ph> is able to use global policies for all
                            agents as well as group policy for group-owned machines to conduct the
                            patching process on multiple devices, before you select agent version
                            please note the following: <ul id="ul_gtf_ckk_n5b">
                                <li>
                                    <p>Global policy is the default agent landing policy, so every
                                        agent will apply this policy first before moving to other
                                        groups. We suggest that the global policy should use lower
                                        agent version as its base policy.</p>
                                </li>
                                <li>
                                    <p>If you don't want to set any agent version for patch
                                        deployment, please unclick all checkboxes next to the agent
                                        version patch files in the <uicontrol>Patch</uicontrol>
                                        section.</p>
                                </li>
                            </ul></p>
                    </note>
                </info>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_tt4_tkk_n5b" type="important">
                        <p><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/PRODUCT_SP_ALTERNATIVE_NAME"
                                >OFFICIAL_PRODUCT_NAME</ph>
                            <?oxy_custom_start type="oxy_content_highlight" color="255,255,0"?>Agent
                            1.0 <?oxy_custom_end?>does not support remote patch because it does not
                            have any available remote patch files.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
