<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Real-Time
        Scan<?oxy_custom_start type="oxy_content_highlight" color="153,255,255"?></title><?oxy_custom_end?>
    <taskbody>
        <context id="context_jww_5n4_n5b">
            <p><uicontrol>Real-time Scan</uicontrol> provides persistent and ongoing file scan for
                the endpoints. Each time a file is received, opened, downloaded, copied, or
                modified, <uicontrol>Real-time Scan</uicontrol> always scans the file for security
                assessment. After performing the <uicontrol>Real-time Scan</uicontrol>, users can
                proceed to access the file if it does not pose a security threat. However, if a
                security risk or possible virus/malware has been detected during the scanning, a
                notification message appears indicating the name of the infected file and the
                specific security risk.</p>
            <p>Moreover, a persistent scan cache is maintained and reloaded each time the
                    <uicontrol>Real-time Scan</uicontrol> is executed. The <uicontrol>Real-time
                    Scan</uicontrol> tracks any changes made to files or folders that have occurred
                until the function is disabled and the files are unloaded and removed from the scan
                cache.</p>
            <note id="note_yn3_jnp_xvb">
                <?oxy_custom_start type="oxy_content_highlight" color="153,255,255"?>
                <p><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/PRODUCT_SPLM_ALTERNATIVE_NAME">OFFICIAL_PRODUCT_NAME</ph>
                    installed on Windows 2000 SP4 (without update rollup) or Windows XP SP1 supports
                    real-time malware scan only when files are opened or executed; it does not
                    support real-time malware scan when files are newly added or
                    changed.<?oxy_custom_end?></p>
            </note>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>All</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/POLICY"/></cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_kqb_dvc_jvb">
                        <p><ph conkeyref="PRODvars/POLICY_NOTE"/></p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to the <uicontrol>Real-Time Scan</uicontrol> in the <uicontrol>Anti-Malware
                        Scanning</uicontrol> section.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Enable the <uicontrol>Real-Time Scan </uicontrol> by simply clicking the toggle
                    to switch it on.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_wr1_hz4_n5b">
                        <p>You can refer to the
                                <?oxy_custom_start type="oxy_content_highlight" color="153,255,255"?><xref
                                href="ScanAdvancedSettings=20220815151900.xml">Advanced
                                Settings</xref><?oxy_custom_end?> for more configurations for the
                            types of the files to be scanned, the action after possible security
                            risk is detected, and the scan exclusion list.</p>
                    </note>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
