<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE task PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Task//EN" "task.dtd"[]>

<task id="GUID-BED80320-70E5-47C4-9530-CC26073D469D" xml:lang="en-us">
    <title id="GUID-71E6E7FF-D420-465A-9CFA-86F8BA5BE094">Configure Maintenance Mode</title>
    <taskbody>
        <context>
            <p>To perform file updates on endpoints, users can configure Maintenance Mode to define
                a period when the agents allows all file executions and adds all files that are
                created, executed, or modified to the Approved List. The agents can learn the
                newly-added applications and ensure the execution of these applications are under
                protection. In addition, during the maintenance period, all newly-added files can be
                updated along with real-time virus scan for consistent security. <note
                    id="note_awv_pvb_s5b">
                    <p>If users change the policy settings of Application Lockdown, OT Application
                        Safeguard, and Real-Time Malware Scan during maintenance period, the policy
                        settings will not be enforced until the maintenance period is ended.</p>
                </note></p>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step>
                <cmd>Go to <menucascade>
                        <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol>
                        <uicontrol>All</uicontrol>
                    </menucascade>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the <uicontrol>All </uicontrol>group on the <uicontrol>Agents</uicontrol>
                    screen. The <wintitle>Agents</wintitle> screen displays a list of agents managed
                    by StellarOne.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Select one or more endpoints (agents or groups) by clicking the checkboxes next
                    to them.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click the <uicontrol>Protection</uicontrol> button from the Tool Bar at the top
                    of the <wintitle>Agents</wintitle> screen.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>A pop-up window appears. Click the <uicontrol>Configure Maintenace
                        Mode</uicontrol> option.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click <uicontrol>Confirm</uicontrol>.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>The configuration window appears. Please read the notice and check either
                        <uicontrol>Enable</uicontrol> or <uicontrol>Disable</uicontrol> radio
                    button.</cmd>
                <choices id="choices_m1n_qjx_j5b">
                    <choice>
                        <p>Click <uicontrol>Enable</uicontrol> to start the Maintenance Mode
                            settings. Please go to Step 8 for next procedure.</p>
                    </choice>
                    <choice>
                        <p>Click <menucascade>
                                <uicontrol>Disable</uicontrol>
                                <uicontrol>OK</uicontrol>
                            </menucascade> to end Maintenance Mode. This will cancel the scheduled
                            maintenance period on endpoints.</p>
                        <ol id="ol_kgd_clx_j5b">
                            <li>
                                <p>A warning message appears. Please read carefully before
                                    proceeding to next step.<note id="note_jh3_yyx_j5b"
                                        type="important">
                                        <p>If the Maintenance Mode is ended, the endpoint will start
                                            blocking the execution of files that are not recognized
                                            by the Application Lockdown and OT Application
                                            Safeguard.</p>
                                    </note></p>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <p>Click <uicontrol>OK</uicontrol> to end Maintenance Mode. A pop-up
                                    window appears showing the deployment status of stopping
                                    Maintenance Mode on endpoints.</p>
                            </li>
                        </ol>
                    </choice>
                </choices>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>The schedule configuration window appears. Do one of the following for
                    scheduling Maintenance Mode.</cmd>
                <choices id="choices_tq3_5zx_j5b">
                    <choice>
                        <p>Click the <uicontrol>Schedule</uicontrol> radio button, and then click
                            the edit icon to select the start date and specify the start time for
                            Maintenance Mode. After that, specify the duration of the maintenance
                            period in <uicontrol>Maintenance Mode will be ended
                            after</uicontrol>.</p>
                    </choice>
                    <choice>
                        <p>Click the <uicontrol>Start now</uicontrol> radio button, and then specify
                            the duration of the maintenance period in <uicontrol>Maintenance Mode
                                will be ended after</uicontrol>.</p>
                    </choice>
                </choices>
            </step>
            <?oxy_custom_start type="oxy_content_highlight" color="153,255,255"?>
            <step>
                <cmd>A toggle switch for enabling/disabling <uicontrol>Real-Time Malware
                        Scan</uicontrol> is added under the Maintenance Mode option. The default
                    setting is ON.</cmd>
                <info>
                    <note id="note_xbf_yzy_j5b">
                        <ul id="ul_tlv_3bz_j5b">
                            <li>
                                <p>If users disable <uicontrol>Real-Time Malware Scan</uicontrol> in
                                    the policy settings, it is reommended to enable the
                                        <uicontrol>Real-Time Malware Scan</uicontrol> toggle switch
                                    here during maintenance period to ensure seamless protection.
                                    After maintenance period ends, the system will follow the
                                    original policy settings (in which the Real-Time Malware Scan is
                                    disabled).</p>
                            </li>
                            <li>
                                <p>Please refer to <xref href="realTimeScan=20220813041755.xml"/>
                                    for more details.</p>
                            </li>
                        </ul>
                    </note>
                    <fig id="fig_kzg_fmk_jvb">
                        <title>StellarProtect MTM</title>
                        <image href="../images/mtm_sp=20221101163308.png" id="image_nsz_fmk_jvb"/>
                    </fig>
                </info>
            </step><?oxy_custom_end?>
            <step>
                <?oxy_custom_start type="oxy_content_highlight" color="255,255,0"?>
                <cmd>For StellarProtect (Legacy Mode)</cmd><?oxy_custom_end?>
                <info>
                    <fig id="fig_mw1_3mk_jvb">
                        <title>StellarProtect (Legacy Mode) MTM</title>
                        <image href="../images/mtm_splm=20221101163400.png" id="image_inj_3mk_jvb"/>
                    </fig>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>Click <uicontrol>OK</uicontrol> to deploy the settings to the selected agents
                    or groups.</cmd>
            </step>
            <step>
                <cmd>The <wintitle>Command Deployment</wintitle> window appears showing the
                    deployment status. Click the <uicontrol>Close</uicontrol> button to close the
                    window.</cmd>
            </step>
        </steps>
    </taskbody>
</task>
